SURESH CARPENTER



- sureshc38@gmail.com
- **&** 8989403617 / 9425444216
- Suthalia Road, Ravishankar Colo ny, Biaora



Team Leading

Problem Solving

Expert in Management

School Classes And Students

Arrangement



Singing Song

Listening Music

LANGUAGE

Expert in English

Expert in Hindi

OBJECTIVE

As a public educator with nearly 7 years of experience in the schools, I am seeking the opportunity to serve as a high school principal in my local community. I am eager to use my proven leadership skills to continue the district's legacy of quality education and help prepare students for future success.

EXPERIENCE

Principal (M.P. Board)

- More than 3 Years

Shanti International School, Pachore (2020-Present) & Subhash Vidhya Niketan, Mau (2017-19) I am handling all kind of school based activities and management work.

English Teacher (TGT) - CBSE

From 2015 - 3 Years

R.K. Academy, Biaora (2015-16) & I.P.S. Academy, Biaora (2016-17) & Prof. Santosh Mittal Higher Secondary School, Pachore (2019-20) I handled English subject in the classes up to 9th Standard.

Business Developer

2014 - 2015

Creative Thoughts Informatic Pvt Ltd, Indore To handle all kind of Website and Application related projects and to deliver the same on time to the clients.

Technical Support Associate

2013 - 2014

Asus India Pvt Ltd, Indore

To handle all kind of customer's gueries related to the products.

EDUCATION

M.A. (English) B.U. Bhopal	2020
B.E. (ECE) RGPV Bhopal	2013
D.El.Ed. NIOS	2019
12th MP Board	2009
10th MP Board	2007



Mobile Controlled Home Appliances

This instrument is helpful for us to control all kind of home appliances by mobile phone.

Made in College Time.

Light Fence

This instrument helps us to protect from unauthorised accesses.

Made in College Time.

R ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

Received Certificate in Sports and Others.

Received Medal in School for scoring Good Marks.

SURESH CARPENTER